<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AzureDVBB&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://azuredvbb.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AzureDVBB&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 12:44:03 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://azuredvbb.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Challenge 001 - Fibonacci Numbers</title>
      <link>https://azuredvbb.github.io/coding_challenges/challenge-001-fibonacci-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 12:44:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azuredvbb.github.io/coding_challenges/challenge-001-fibonacci-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Objectives create a command-line application to calculate the n-th fibonacci number accepts 1 command-line argument n (integer between 1 and 80) result is printed to the console (standard output) Introduction The Fibonacci numbers which form the Fibonacci sequence are a classic mathematical concept that is both easy to implement in code and hard to actually compute for any n-th Fibonacci number.
Devilishly simple to understand and having a myraid of formulas to calculate it, and even more ways to implement it, each having it&amp;rsquo;s own trade-offs make it a good challenge candidate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding Challenge 000 - Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://azuredvbb.github.io/coding_challenges/challenge_000_hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 16:29:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azuredvbb.github.io/coding_challenges/challenge_000_hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Objectives Summary Set up the development environment Create a stand-alone executable Print &amp;ldquo;Hello Wolrd!&amp;rdquo; into a console when run Introduction Hello there! Welcome to my own list of coding challenges born from frustrations with the google results to &amp;lsquo;coding challenge&amp;rsquo; being either not related or subscription services.
Already planning on learning a few new languages, I figured the best way to do so is set a nice gauntlet of challenges to myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo on Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://azuredvbb.github.io/posts/hugo-on-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 11:54:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azuredvbb.github.io/posts/hugo-on-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>With guides it is easy, but it took me a while to google out the answer, so I shall leave the steps to take generating a HUGO website and posting it onto github for future reference.
You will need git and hugo installed for this.
This guide expects you to be familiar with the command line and Github, as well as having read the quick-start guide on HUGO.
Step 0. - (LINUX) Make sure you have github ssh key setup Step 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YUMS - A retrospective</title>
      <link>https://azuredvbb.github.io/posts/yums-a-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 16:53:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azuredvbb.github.io/posts/yums-a-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>This is a blog post for the archival of my YUMS project.
We had a good run, a month of development that taught me much. But in the end. It all ends the same. Just another bowl of &amp;ldquo;modular&amp;rdquo; sphagetti.
What was the plan? A simple, barebones implementation that is extendable and scalable. It also should use as few dependancies as possible.
There was already an immensely more mature and batteries included framework called Evennia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://azuredvbb.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 16:06:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azuredvbb.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my corner of the internet! This is primarily the place where I keep my notes on the open source projects and repositories I make, or summary posts of things I have learned.
Hopefully watching the barren landscape here will keep me motivated on doing more stuff!
Take a beverage of your choice and have a pleasant read! (note: may contain ramblings)
Who am I? Just a hobby programmer/gamer sharing my knowledge across the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
